Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar
and brother, as you all know,
I work here in ICICI Bank.
Brother, the topic of today's video is
going to be,
you must have already seen it in the title and thumbnail.
Brother, I have received a lot of messages.  I have been
personally asked here.
And brother, I
also get to see a lot of comments.
Many times I also get to see messages here from people
who personally
message me.  Those brothers ask this,
especially the freshers, many
people want to do jobs, those who
want to come in the banking sector, they
want to do jobs in the banking sector, so brother they think
that what is target pressure?  If
we do not pressurize the target or if we do
not complete the target, will the
bank expel you or is there some other session for it,
if you do not complete the target
then what is done to you,
friends, regarding this, this question is going to be asked,
friends, regarding this,
I am going to explain to you in detail here that
if you
work in any banking bank and
your target is not completed there.
Especially if you are in sales, there is
100% sales in the bank.  If
you go for the job of a sales officer, then brother,
you have targets and pressure
too.  Brother, if your target is
not completed then what can happen to you
?  Brother, will the bank expel you?
Friends, I am going to tell you the answer to this in full detail in today's video.
Friends, if you like this video then please
like the video.  If
you are new to this channel, then friends,
please subscribe to the channel
because you will keep getting helpful content here.  First of all
friends, let me give you an
update.  We have DBS
Bank, HDFC Bank and
Indusland Bank, friends, hiring is going on in all these three banks,
HDFC DBS and Indusand Bank. Whatever
I have told in my group
about DBS Bank, I had told about its hiring here in the
morning, I had posted here on
my WhatsApp, if you have
not joined the WhatsApp group here yet, the
link is given below, go and
join the group here friends,
you will keep getting new updates there.
Here we are talking about if you are
selected in a bank,
you are selected for the post of a sales person
and friends, you are given a target here,
like I take my own,
I am already working in ICICI Bank.
Friends, I am in sales.
Currently, I am a sales officer and
I am customer active.  Brother,
my work here is also
in the corporate card and business card department.
We also have a
target.  Brother, the target given to us is
10 to 15 cards per month,
which we have to
achieve here.  You can do that any way you want.
We also get data etc. and
brother, we also have to go to the customer.
Meetings etc. also have to be arranged.
Brother, if we are not able to complete it here then
what happens brother?  First of all
friends, you will have to accept this if brother you are
coming into the banking sector.  If you
want to work in the banking sector, then
brother, you will have to complete the targets given to you.  You
can do it in any way you want, you can do it sitting at home,
you can do it by going to the office,
or you can do it by going to the market.
Like we are given a target of 15 cards.  Out of that,
if brother,
we complete the target between 10 to 12.  If we
complete our cards then
brother, no one will
say anything to us.  Your boss will put some
pressure on you.  He will
ask you, what is happening?  What is
not happening?  Friends, this is your 100% guarantee that
if you are on roll in the bank, then the
bank cannot remove you like this at all.
Your boss can only listen to you.
Friends, you will be waited here for 6 months.
If brother, you do
not give anything within 6 months.  This business remains at 0%.  That
means, if you do not complete even a single transaction in the entire month or
within the entire 6 months, then the
bank will take your
resignation.  You will have to resign yourself.
Your boss will also tell you to
resign.  You will receive
two warning letters from the bank.  In that, you will be
given the first warning letter that you should do the business.
Otherwise you will be terminated.
Brother, in a second
no mail etc. will come to you here.  If brother,
you do not do business, your boss
reports to him that brother, there is no business.  If it is at
zero then brother, they will directly
terminate you.  We will take your
registration here.  You will have to
resign yourself.  Therefore, friends,
here I am telling you that
if you do it for 6 months, if you
remain at zero for 6 months, then only then the
bank can withdraw your money.  Brother, if you complete three
to four or five to six targets, even if
you complete 50% of them, then
you have been given 12 cards.
If you complete even five to six cards, then
brother, the bank will
not be able to harm you in any way.  Your job here is 100%
secure.  It is safe.   This is the only little bit
that you will get to hear.  The
boss at your place will
tell you this brother.  We will tell you 100%, target you
and also put pressure on you.
Whatever I tell you, you will have to listen to it.
Friends, if you want to survive in the banking sector, then
you will have to listen.
You will have to do sales if you come into sales brother.
Friends, here you have a target
and brother, you also have pressure.  Rest of the
brothers, many people had asked me
that if your target is not completed then
what will happen to you here, then brother,
I have told you that nothing will be done to you for 6 months.
If brother,
you do not do anything here for 6 months, then
obviously you will have to go here
because brother, the bank is
not giving you free salary.  The bank is providing you
salary for the work you are doing.
Rest of the brothers, you should do
your work here with full concentration.  Rest of the brothers, it is
not that they are not targeted.  Sales happen.
100% friends, there is sale here.
100% targets are completed.  Brothers are
earning incentives up to ₹30-40, ₹400 here.  The
brothers who are with us,
earn ₹300 incentive in 2020.  Many
people who have experience of 3 to 4 years, they
earn incentives of ₹30 to ₹35,000 here and
put it in their pocket, their salary is already there, plus the ₹
300 incentive of ₹20 to 300 from here, they
put that in their pocket here.
Brother, their target is also completed 100%.
If brother, you want to do it,
if brother, you are passionate and you want to do it, then
brother, your target is 100% completed.
100% friends, you achieve the target that you have given yourself.  There
is nothing to worry about.  Brother, the
target and pressure is going to be 100% in the banking sector.
Brothers who are freshers,
this video is going to be a must watch here.
You see for yourself.  There
is no need to panic like this.  If you are a fresher, you will
also gain experience.  As
you gain experience,
your confidence will increase and brother,
you will not consider the target and pressure to be that much.
Ok?  That means you will be
able to handle it comfortably.  Rest brother, I have
answered it here.  So brother, this was the
answer.  Rest of the brothers, if you want to get the
job of HDFC Sales Officer, then
friends, we have
hiring going on for it.  The link is given below,
please join the WhatsApp group.
You will also get my personal number there.
Friends, you can also join there here.  You
can also DM me and
take personal guidance.  Also
friends, let me tell you one more update.
If brother, you
want to know about BFSI sector.  Friends, here
I have launched an
e-book about BFSI sector.  If brother,
you want to go, if brother, you want to know
about that sector here.  Friends, in this,
two to three products will be provided to you here.
First friends, the
e-book will be provided to you.  Second
friends, my personal resume here,
I am going to
give you its template as a demo.  So
friends, after seeing that, you can also get your resume made here.
Its price is going to be Rs 69, in which
we will
also conduct your interview here.
My personal guidance here will also be
available to you for free.   The
rest is up to you brother.  If brother, you
want to take it here, then brother,
you can comment in the comment box below
or you can also message me on WhatsApp.
You will get it here.   It is
only for ₹69.  If you want to take it, you can take it.
If you
know about the BFSI sector, please
DM me below.  Please share your CV with me.  Please
share your CV with me.  Brother, let me
conduct your interview here.
Rest friends, this is all I have told you in today's video.
You must have got the answer to what I have told you.
I hope you liked this video very much.  If you like the
video then please like it.
If brother, you have not yet subscribed to this channel, then
brother,
go quickly and subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.  Tak ke, take
care.